The Vow is a drama, romance film directed by Michael Sucsy.
Happy young married couple Paige and Leo are, well, happy.
Then a car accident puts Paige into a life-threatening coma.
Upon awakening she has lost the previous five years of memories, including those of her beloved Leo, her wedding,
a confusing relationship with her parents, or the ending of her relationship with her ex-fiance.
Despite these complications, Leo endeavors to win her
heart again and rebuild their marriage.
Paige Collins, played by Rachel McAdams.
Leo Collins, played by Channing Tatum.
Bill Thornton, played by Sam Neill.
Jeremy, played by Scott Speedman.
Rita Thornton, played by Jessica Lange.
Lily, played by Tatiana Maslany.
The Vow is a 2012 American romantic drama film directed by Michael
Sucsy and starring Rachel McAdams and Channing Tatum.
Written by Abby Kohn, Marc Silverstein, and Jason Katims, the film was
inspired by the true story of Kim and Krickitt Carpenter.
In addition to McAdams and Tatum as Paige and Leo Collins, the cast includes Sam Neill,
Scott Speedman, Jessica Lange and Jessica McNamee in supporting roles.
As of 2013, The Vow was the eighth highest-grossing
romantic drama film produced since 1980.
This was Spyglass Entertainment's last film before the
company's closure in 2012 and its revival in 2019.
The film explores themes of amnesia, coma, based on
true story, romance, memory loss.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.